Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Professor Ray J. Wu in laboratory at Wing Hall (People-- Portraits), May 1978; 564; 21 (Box 17)
  - HDFS student (Susan Silverman) working with older adults at Ithacare (Child Dev. And Family Relationships--Older People), May 12, 1978; 565; 20 (Box 17)
  - Bulletin covers (Bulletins), Winter-Spring 1978; 566; 37 (Box 17)
  - Dean Failing's Retirement, May 25, 1978; 567; 103 (Box 17)
  - Dinner honoring Joseph King--sponsored by Rochester Cornell Clubs (Organizations--Cornell Extension Clubs), May 18, 1978; 568; 149 (Box 17)
  - HE Graduation, May 1978; 569; 439 (Box 17)
  - Home Study student visits Cornell campus. Wayne White and family (Economics), June 5, 1978; 570; 14 (Box 17)
  - Cover picture for bulletin "4-H Dairy Project" M-4-3. Rita Carey with calf (Bulletins), June 1, 1978; 571; 77 (Box 17)
  - HE students. Sheet #1--Neva James, Don Liff, Pat Warner; Sheet #2--Ken Leman, Neva James; Sheet #3--Rhonda Shapiro., May 17, 1978; 572; 49 (Box 17)
  - Sheets #1-5: Photos of T & R Beef Center at Harford, NY (Beef Cattle Research), June 1978; 573; 161 (Box 17)
  - Sheets #6&7: Open House at Harford Teaching and Research Center (Beef Cattle Research), June 11, 1978; 573; 55 (Box 17)
  - Sheet #8: Lab Scenes, 573; 8 (Box 17)
  - Frame scroll presented to Prof. Emeritus "Tip" Porter at 106 Linn Street; Prof. Porter's home (Presentations), June 9, 1978; 574; 13 (Box 17)
  - County agents at work: Sheet #1: Onondaga County agents--Frank Hyatt, Donna Curcio, Walter G. Newhauser, June 1978; 575; 48 (Box 17)
  - Sheet #2: Tompkins County agriculture aid--Penny Cook, June 1978; 575; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Sheet #3: Country Agent In Service, Jean McLean's textile class being taught by Jean McLean and Connie Adams, June 1978; 575; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Sheet #4: Gordon Madison & Glenn Griffin, June 1978; 575; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Walls, halls, staircase and doorways of first floor Roberts (Cornell University Buildings/Roberts Hall), June 1978; 576; 36 (Box 17)
  - Photos of empty spots from falling bricks on Bradfield Hall (Cornell University/Agronomy Building), June 1978; 577; 98 (Box 17)
  - Buildings on state campus needing repair (Cornell Univ. Buildings), July 1978; 578; 161 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 5: Obsolete lab in Plant Pathology/Plant Sci., Oct. 1978; 578; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Soft goods for NASA Space Shuttle Program to be used for HE promotion "Functional Clothing", June 1978, Dec. 1978; 579; 60 (Box 17)
  - Field north of Skaneateles Lake (Field Crops), Early 1970's; 580; no number given (Box 17)
  - B & PA faculty members & administrators at Malott Hall. To be used for brochure designed by Sue Hartman, Aug. 1978; 581; 72 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Robert Foote in lab in Morrison Hall (Lab Scenes), Aug. 1978; 582; 70 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 1: Dave Stipanuk next to his Solar Collector, Aug. 1978; 583; 72 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 2: Dave Stipanuk next to his Solar Collector and also energy wood burning photos, Aug. 1978; 583; * (Box 17)
  - Sheet 3: Lois Post home fireplace, Nov. 1978; 583; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Sheet 4: Cookstove and at home of Mrs. Helen Jackson/Enfield, Jan. 1979; 583; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Sheet 5: Man cleaning chimney, Nov. 1978; 583; No. of Negs: (Box 17)
  - Dean Dave Call at his desk in Roberts Hall, Aug. 1978; 584; 47 (Box 17)
  - Photos taken showing how a girl with Down's Syndrome spends her day. Taken for use in HE forum Vol. 9-2, Aug. 1978; 585; 96 (Box 17)
  - Campus Scenes--Sheet 1& 2 Ag. Quad, Sheet 3: Exterior MVR, Sept. 1978 & Oct. 1978; 586; 93 (Box 17)
  - Ag. School registration in Barton Hall (CU Activities), Sept. 1978; 587; 20 (Box 17)
  - State Fair 1978--Food and Nutrition exhibit, Sept. 1978; 588; 30 (Box 17)
  - Agents Training--Energy consumption of various appliances (Organizations/Extension Service), Sept. 1978; 589; 31 (Box 17)
  - New agents taken at 1978 orientation (Organization/Ext. Serv.), Oct. 1978; 590; 188 (Box 17)
  - Waiter Vegera in Waste Management Lab at Riley Robb (People--Portraits), Oct. 1978; 591; 22 (Box 17)
  - Chancellor Wharton of SUNY visit to State School of Cornell University (People--Faculty), Oct. 27, 1978; 592; 65 (Box 17)
  - The passing of the "Directors Hat" (Issac P. Roberts silk hat) from former Dean W. Keith Kennedy to Dean David Call (Cornell University Activities), Oct. 1978; 593; 46 (Box 17)
  - Students at a computer terminal in Morrison Hall (Campus scenes--Resident Teaching--Ag. College), Oct. 31, 1978; 594; 24 (Box 17)
  - Students using fabric testing machines and other lab equipment (Textiles Clothing--Research, Textile Testing), Nov. 1, 1978; 595; 83 (Box 17)
  - Photographs showing packaging of new products developed in Poultry Science (Economics--Marketing), Oct. 1978; 596; 46 (Box 17)
  - Photographs of typical office scenes to be used in Career's Brochure (People), Sept. 1978; 597; 61 (Box 17)
  - Prof. Dorothy Nelkin (Sh.1), Prof. M. Esman & Sec. (Sh. 2), Prof. D. Ashford (Sh. 3) (People-faculty Groups) For use in B. & PA Brochure, Nov. 1978; 598; 64 (Box 17)
  - Teaching Conference--Human Ecology Faculty at Clark Hall (Human Ecology Activities) (The Art of Excellent Teaching), Nov. 1978; 599; 129 (Box 17)
  - Cindy Noble--Extension Director at meeting in Room 8, Roberts Hall (People--Faculty), Nov. 1978; 600; 10 (Box 17)
  - Open house at Resource Information Lab (Cornell University Activities), Nov. 1978; 601; 21 (Box 17)
  - James Estes at his drawing table. Taken for ACE publicity, Dec. 1978; 602; 36 (Box 17)
  - David Lane/Comm. Arts grad student. Photos to be used in Farm Journal, Dec. 1978; 603; 31 (Box 17)
  - Ice and snow damage on Comstock Knoll of Arboretum (Campus Scenes--Weather), Dec. 1978; 604; 56 (Box 17)
  - Lab and woodworking shop scenes, taken in DEA at MVR (Housing & Design/Resident Teaching), Nov. 1978; 605; 100 (Box 17)
  - Conference --Alcoholism and the Family (Child Dev./Family Life Conferences), Sept. 1978; 606; 31 (Box 17)
  - HE Open House, Nov. 1978; 607; 130 (Box 17)
  - Cornell student teachers at Boynton Jr. High School (Education/HE Student Teaching), Oct. 1978; 608; 28 (Box 17)
  - Economic Opportunity Day--students from all over New York State listening to overview of programs for Human Ecology (Education--Human Ecology students), Nov. 14, 1978; 609; 18 (Box 17)
  - Chris Yackel setting up costume display on 2nd floor of MVR (Textiles & Clothing/Costume Collection), Oct. 1978; 610; 18 (Box 17)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute Activities--1979. To be used for BTI Annual Report, Jan. 1979; 611; 470 (Box 17)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey professors--candid shots at work. Sheet 1: Dr. Frederer/Warren Hall; Sheet 2: Dr. McCormick/ Savage Hall; Sheet 2: Dr. Hal Moore/Mann Lib. (CU Resident Teaching), Jan. 1979; 612; 70 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Edgar Raffensperger--Entomology--using innovative teaching techniques. To be used in Ag. School Alumni Newsletter (CU Resident Teaching), Jan. 1979; 613; 27 (Box 17)
  - Photos of children in eating situations. Children from Human Ecology Nursery School (Food and Nut./Research), Feb. 15, 1979; 614; 240 (Box 17)
  - Entomology faculty (People--Faculty Groups), Feb. 1979; 615; 154 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Pechuman (Entomology) working with insect collection. Frames 24-37/ Microscope for Entomology, Feb. 1979; 616; 37 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Hansel (Animal Science) in lab and office at Multicat Building, Feb. 1979; 617; 22 (Box 17)
  - Luciano Corazza working with new technique for feeding trout fingerlings/ and working with Walleye Pike. Mike Jahncke with pike, Feb. 1979; 618; 62 (Box 17)
  - Dean's Garden behind Warren Hall, Feb. 1979; 619; 8 (Box 17)
  - Career Center in Roberts Hall, Feb. 1979; 620; 10 (Box 17)
  - Pomology students using microscopes in lab, Feb. 1979; 621; 9 (Box 17)
  - Dean Ziegler and two students who won the Golden Phone award for Human Ecology (CU Awards) To be used for HE Alumni News (Sheet 1), Mar. 9, 1979; 622; 10 (Box 17)
  - Kathie Young at her home in Truxton, NY, with self designed herb drying cabinet and home canned food (Sheet 2), Mar. 20, 1979; 622; 23 (Box 17)
  - Patricia Carter--student/MVR Faculty Commons (Sheet 3), Mar. 1979; 622; 20 (Box 17)
  - Students (Marcia Sigal, Kristen Holmes) working on new newsletter (Sheets 4 & 5), Apr. 1979; 622; 23 (Box 17)
  - Recruiting Staff (Peter Holmes, Beth Martin, Helen Pape, Dave Liberature, Steve Leigh and Staff photo, Jeanne Rice (Sheet 6), Apr. 1979; 622; 35 (Box 17)
  - Robert Hurd (HE Alumnus at work) at First National Bank, Ithaca NY (People--Portraits), Feb. 28, 1979; 623; 9 (Box 17)
  - Students participating in a nutrition project--Riboflavin Study (Food--Nutrition--Research/Nutrition), Mar. 1979; 624; 11 (Box 17)
  - Ag. Day--taken at Willard Straight Hall, Mar. 1979; 625; 49 (Box 17)
  - Dean Dave Call and M.J. Gourdian and his wife. He is the first recipient of the Borden Scholarship--1945. (People --Foreign Visitors), Mar. 9, 1979; 626; 10 (Box 17)
  - Big-Little-Sister-Brother relationships. Taken at Lynah Rink. Some of the grown people in the photos are HE students, Mar. 14, 1979; 627; 65 (Box 17)
  - Students in textile lab in MVR, Feb. 1979; 628; 29 (Box 17)
  - Costume Collection (Clothing Design), Apr. 1979; 629; 124 (Box 17)
  - Syracuse Project (Dr. Bronfrenbrenner/Family Matters), Mar. 1979; 630; 165 (Box 17)
  - CSE Corning Project--Nancy Saltzford, Mar 1979; 631; 93 (Box 17)
  - Students in Plant Path lab examining spare counting device. (Phil Arneson's class) To be used in F & L Sciences Quarterly, Jan. 1979; 632; 30 (Box 17)
  - NYC Field Study--Corporate Connection (T. Stanton), Mar. 1979; 633; 186 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Elfing examining equipment used to protect apples from Pollution damage, Summer 1979; 634; 33 (Box 17)
  - CSE Social work sequence (J. Meuller), Mar. 1979; 635; 77 (Box 17)
  - 1979 Human Ecology Activities; Sheet 1: Construction in MVR, Apr. 1979; 636; 28 (Box 17)
  - Sheets 2 & 3: Research in Nutritional Life Sciences, Dr. Zilversmith's Lab, Apr. 1979; 636; 74 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 4: Field study Reception, Students in hall of MVR drawing, Nov. 1979; 636; 32 (Box 17)
  - 75th Anniversary of Ag. College, May 12, 1979; 637; 556 (Box 17)
  - HANDIVAN in front of Bailey Hall, Apr. 19, 1979; 638; 13 (Box 17)
  - Design studio--Third year, Steve Mensch's class in MVR, May 1979; 639; 24 (Box 17)
  - HE student profiles, May 1979; 640; 105 (Box 17)
  - HE student teacher in Watkin's Glen School (Laura Paradzick/CSE), Dec. 1979; 641; 35 (Box 17)
  - New York City/Sea Grant photos, May 1979; 642; 222 (Box 17)
  - Dedication of Room 131 in Roberts Hall in memory of George S. Butts, June 1979; 643; 24 (Box 17)
  - Human Ecology Forum; Sheet 1: John Condry, Prof. HDFS and James Titus, June 1979; 644; 10 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 2: John Condry, Prof. HDFS and James Titus, July 1979; 644; 34 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 3: HE Nursery schoolroom with George Lavaris & Jan Crance; vines on a fence, Oct. 1979; 644; 12 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 4: HE Nursery schoolroom with George Lavaris & Jan Crance, Oct. 1979; 644; 11 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 5: Vines on a fence, Oct. 1979; 644; 9 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 6: Foreman, schoolteacher, mother & child, Dec. 1979; 644; 12 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 7: Photo of counter and shoppers at Sears, Jan. 1980; 644; 19 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 8: Expectant couple in front of painting of child (Sue Hartman has taken negs permanently), Jan. 1980; 644; 32 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 9: Simulated auditorium seating, Jan. 1980; 644; 12 (Box 17)
  - Sheet 10: Photos showing gas shortage, Jan. 1980; 644; 12 (Box 17)
  - Sheets 11-14: Governor's Conference, Feb. 1980; 644; 117 (Box 17)
  - Photographs taken of Shelley Kath, Eva Desmond and Rich Luciani to be used for HE Announcement cover, June 21, 1979; 645; 18 (Box 17)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; NO. of Negs. (Box BOX)
  - HE Graduation, May 1979; 646; no number given (Box 18)
  - Children in food situations, lectures, etc., June 1979; 647; 59 (Box 18)
  - Interview of Urie Brofenbrenner by James Titus, July 3, 1979; 648; 28 (Box 18)
  - Dedication of room 37 in Plant Science in honor of Laurence H. McDaniels of Floriculture, June 1979; 649; 30 (Box 18)
  - Luncheon and tour of Cornell University Plantations sponsors, June 1979; 650; 50 (Box 18)
  - Sheet 1: Sex stereotyping workshop, Fall 1978; 651; 35 (Box 18)
  - Sheet 2: Housing class (Barbara Osgood's) at Longhouse on West Hill, Fall 1978; 651; 15 (Box 18)
  - Sheet 3: Barbara Osgood's Housing class at Savanna Condominium, Fall 1978; 651; 12 (Box 18)
  - Garbage, Aug. 1979; 652; 62 (Box 18)
  - Marilyn McKay & Glen Appleby recruiting for career in Coop. Extension brochure, Aug. 1979; 653; 46 (Box 18)
  - Grinding and deboning leghorn chicken backs and necks at Bruckner Lab and Plainfield Turkey Farm, Plainfield, NY., June 1979; 654; 60 (Box 18)
  - Photographs to illustrate a bored college student. John and Pachai and Mario Saraceni, Aug 1979; 655; 18 (Box 18)
  - Model Home model/prototype, Sept. 1979; 656; 19 (Box 18)
  - Chinese Delegation, Sept. 1979; 657; 11 (Box 18)
  - State Fair--Blood Brother Ceremony. Bill Umschied is made a blood brother, Sept. 1979; 658; 20 (Box 18)
  - Montgomery Wards television display, Fays Drugs--Vitamin display and Slaterville Springs Post Office (HE Forum), Aug. 1979; 659; 30 (Box 18)
  - Dolls--designed by Rainee Crawford, made by Valerie Fuller. Dolls on HE Nursery School Playground, in Photo Studio. To be used in HE Forum (College of HE--HE Forum), Sept. 1979; 660; 75 (Box 18)
  - Dean Jerome Ziegler at his desk, Sept. 1979; 661; 71 (Box 18)
  - State Fair 1979, Sept. 1979; 662; 109 (Box 18)
  - Brenda Bricker/Director of Admissions--Human Ecology, Sept. 1979; 663; 13 (Box 18)
  - Robert Barker in his lab/Bio. Chemistry and Joseph M. Calvo at his desk/Associate Professor Biochem. Molec. Cell. Biology--211 Wing Hall, Sept. 1979; 664; 30 (Box 18)
  - Orientation minority students candid photos, Aug. 30, 1979; 665; 35 (Box 18)
  - Environmental portrait of Clarence Reed, Jr. (student), Sept. 4, 1979; 666; 9 (Box 18)
  - Melanie Ng--Cornell University graduate at Agronomy greenhouse, Sept. 9, 1979; 667; 23 (Box 18)
  - House and Bank Photos. To be used in Buying a Home brochure. Sheets 8 & 9: Renting brochure, Rochester, NY. Shs. 10-17, Sept. 1979; 668; 258 (Box 18)
  - Flood of 1972, Hurricane Agnes, June 1972; 669; 32 (Box 18)
  - Campus Scenes, Summer-Fall 1979; 670; 70 (Box 18)
  - (Puddles) a dog costume used by agents to show the proper foods to eat. Puddles & Grandma & other Veg. Puppets. (Nutrition puppets--Dave Watkins, Martha Mapes), Sept. 1979; 671; 18 (Box 18)
  - Alumni case in MVR (Mario Saraceni), Spring 1979; 672; 99 (Box 18)
  - Two assemblymen tour energy projects at T & R Center in Hartford (Assemblymen Kidder and Siegel, Albany), Oct. 12, 1979; 673; 23 (Box 18)
  - New agents taken for 1979 Orientation, Oct. 1979; 674; 34 (Box 18)
  - New contacts of Ellie Peavey/Cortland County, Mar. 1981; 674; 144 (Box 18)
  - Home Study (Lillian Edds, R. Nolan, N. Campbell, Gene German, R. Hawkes, J. Hayes, S. Corbin, G. Pidduck), Oct. 1979; 675; 18 (Box 18)
  - Photographs to show farming in the 1980's, taken at Animal Science Teaching and Research Center, Harford, NY, Oct. 1979; 676; 100, 2color TR. (Box 18)
  - DEA photographs--students working on costumes, Sept. 24, 1979; 677; 30 (Box 18)
  - Steve Hamilton, Assistant Professor Hum. Dev. Family Studies portrait, Oct. 1979; 678; 12 (Box 18)
  - Student Registration, Sept. 1979; 679; 35 (Box 18)
  - BTI, Oct. 1979; 680; 27 (Box 18)
  - Alfalfa Room Dedication (for use in Ag. Pac), Sept. 1979; 681; 26 (Box 18)
  - Books used in CEPP classes, Sept. 1979; 682; 21 (Box 18)
  - Human Services Studies/Micro-teaching in HSS Resource Room, Nov. 1979; 683; 52 (Box 18)
  - Interview between a nutritionist and a mother. Akweley Annan & Carmen Inmink. To be used for a book by Diva Sanjur, Nov. 1979; 684; 23 (Box 18)
  - Human Ecology Symposium, Nov. 1979; 685; 654 (Box 18)
  - Study Center, Principles of Biochem. Course--auto tutorial course taught by Joe Calvo. Students, Joe Calvo, Martha Ferger, Dec. 1979; 686; 56 (Box 18)
  - Photo of student and teacher discussing work. Sue Watkins and student (Zipper Contest), Dec. 1979; 687; 15 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #1, 2, 3: Playground equipment at HE Nursery School at MVR. To be used for Human Ecology News, Dec. 1979; 688; 32 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #4: Staff Sketch Photos. People are Sandy Martin, Margaret Brady Rose Carthame, Patricia Iafrate, Dec. 1979; 688; 51 (Box 18)
  - Human Ecology Annual Report; Sheet #1: Seminar by Scott Thompson/Field Study, Dec. 1979; 689; 7 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #2: Seminar by Mike Johnson/CEH, Dec. 1979; 689; 18 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #3: Campus Life Photos, MVR faculty commons & hallway, Dec. 1979; 689; 16 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #4 & 5: Nutrition Lab photos in MVR, Dec. 1979; 689; 61 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #6 & 7: Candid Design classes in MVR, Dec. 1979; 689; 72 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #8 & 9: Photos at weight lab in Savage Hall, Dec. 1979; 689; 18 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #10: Nursery School candid photos in MVR Nursery School, Dec. 1979; 689; 21 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #11: Nutritionist at Metabolic Unit and Design Presentation (Sue Watkin's class), Dec. 1979; 689; 24 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #12: Martha Mapes--Teaching Nutrition at South Hill School, Dec. 1979; 689; 35 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #13: Gret Atkin and C.C. Chu inspecting Clothing Design Project, Dec. 1979; 689; 13 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #14: CEH Field Study, Lois Lupica & professor, Dec. 1979; 689; 25 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #15: Frames 1-13 Design presentation at 408 MVR; Frames 14A-30 Field Study Presentation at GIAC, Dec. 1979; 689; 29 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #16: Frames 14-19 & 20-24 Debbie Durnham at Bard Hall; Frames 25-29 Norm Campbell testing textiles; Frames 30-37 Jana Percy testing textiles, Dec. 1979; 689; 23 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #17: Lakeside Nursing Home, Jan. 1980; 689; 25 (Box 18)
  - Century Farm farmers and agents (See Folder for names), Summer 1979; 690; 27 color neg. (Box 18)
  - Campus Scenes (Color Transparencies), Summer 1979; 691; 16 color TR, 6 color neg (Box 18)
  - Floriculture student painting in Lou Minns Gardens, Apr. 1979; 691; 7 35 mm B & W (Box 18)
  - Extension Conference at Grossinger's, Liberty, New York, Dec. 1979; 692; 461 (Box 18)
  - Award of Merit recipients, Dairy Days Jan 8-9, 1980, Robert J. Young, Richard Popp, Albert S. Fox, Gordon Conklin, Jan. 8, 1979; 693; 12 (Box 18)
  - Chris Yackel and students working on costumes for Syracuse Opera Company, Jan. 7, 1979; 694; 35 (Box 18)
  - People working in diagnostic lab in Vet College, Feb. 5, 1979; 695; 30 (Box 18)
  - Pine Vol, taken at Research Park. Pine Vol belongs to Peter Brussard, Mar. 1980; 696; 39 (Box 18)
  - Extension agent training for greenhouse structure & misc., Feb. 1980; 697; 30 (Box 18)
  - Elsie Van Buran Rice contest in oral communication, Mar. 1980; 698; 35 (Box 18)
  - BTI activities and architecture photos, Mar. 1980; 699; 416 (Box 18)
  - Barn stalls, cow and calf taken at Animal Science for use in Bulletin "Reproductive Efficiency" IB 162., Mar. 1980; 700; 42 (Box 18)
  - New Extension agents 1980, Mar. 1980; 701; 81 (Box 18)
  - Demonstration booths set up at Pyramid by extension agents, Feb. 1980; 702; 60 (Box 18)
  - Presentation of plaque to Susan Lefitt from Al Stenger--Senior Vice President of American Greetings Corporation; also presentation of certificate to Al Stenger from University Development, Feb. 1980; 703; 13 (Box 18)
  - President of P & C Food Markets speaking to Gene German's class in Warren Hall (Irwin Schwartz), Feb. 1980; 704; 36 (Box 18)
  - Photos of Dean David Call's birthday party at Ag. Pac. Meeting, Feb. 1980; 705; 8 (Box 18)
  - Food Science Faculty, Mar. 1980; 706; 162 (Box 18)
  - Campus scenes, winter and outdoor scenes as seen from MVR window, also faculty lounge in MVR, people leaving football game, Mar. 1980; 707; 132 (Box 18)
  - Guest speaker Richard J. Hersh--President of National Mass Retailing Institute speaking to Gene German's class, Mar. 1980; 708; 36 (Box 18)
  - Staff sketch photos, Dave Parks, William Gauger, Bonnie Huff, Nevart Yaghlain, for use in Human Ecology News, Mar. 1980; 709; 61 (Box 18)
  - Children in exercise positions. Taken for use in NET K-6 Level 2 (Fitness cards), Mar. 1980; 710; 142 (Box 18)
  - Resource Information Lab Workshop, Apr. 1980; 711; 135 (Box 18)
  - Chicken Barbecue at Myers Park, Lansing, NY, Apr. 1980; 712; 12 (Box 18)
  - Cooperative Extension Exhibit with Les Baldwin, Apr. 1980; 713; 7 (Box 18)
  - Ag. & Life Sciences News photos; Sheet #1: Dr. Foote working in his lab with microscope/ bull semen straws; also Candy Cabral (student) brushing cow, Apr. 1980; 714; 42 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #2: Ward Tingey in lab at Old Insectory, Apr. 1980; 714; 34 (Box 18)
  - Department heads: Tim Stanton--Field study, Dr. Nesheim--DNS, Scott Maynes--CEH, Don Bard--CSS, Nancy Saltford--DEA, Phil Schoggen--HDFS, William Sims--DEA, Apr. 1980; 715; 218 (Box 18)
  - People's Republic of China--various Ag. Colleges visited by Dean Call, J.F. Metz, M.L. Barnett, R. J. Young, D.W. Barton and R. J. Kuhr, Mar. 1980; 716; 32 (Box 18)
  - Scholarship donor and recipient dinner at Statler Inn, Apr. 1980; 717; 177 (Box 18)
  - Food photos for Food and Life Sciences Quarterly, May 1980; 718; 113, 1 color neg (Box 18)
  - HE students sitting on ground outside of MVR Hall, May 1980; 719; 12, 6 color neg (Box 18)
  - Guest lecturer for Communication Arts class (Roy Danis/General Wine and Spirits), May 1980; 720; 34 (Box 18)
  - Highway school--1980 (Negs returned to Yong Kim), May 1980; 721; 18 (Box 18)
  - HE Annual Report; Sheet #1: Mary Morrison and students working in DNS Animal Lab, Apr. 29, 1980; 722; 16 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #2-4: Nutritional Sciences Department Activities--Diva Sanjur, Ruth Klippstein, Gertrude Armbruster, S.K. Kumaniyika at Fat Testing Lab, Apr. 29, 1980; 722; 71 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #5-6: Micheal Boyd & student at critique in MVR. DEA, Feb. 21, 1980; 722; 45 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #7: DEA presentation, DEA students & faculty & friends, Feb. 1980; 722; 36 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #8: Chris Yackels' DEA Class Critique, May 1980; 722; 36 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #9: Gret Atkins and C.C. Chu working on wheelchair clothing design, May 1980; 722; 5 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #10: Professor Gerner and students working with computer in Warren Hall (CEH), May 1980; 722; 19 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #11: Grad Seminar in CEH, May 1980; 722; 14 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #12: ETV Radio Center with Bruce Hall and Abbey Frederickson doing a radio spot, Apr. 1980; 722; 8 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #13: Professor Semaj lecturing to HE students in Uris Auditorium (HDFS), Apr. 1980; 722; 20 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #14 & 15: Photos of HDFS students working with Learning Web students, May 1980; 722; 37 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #16: HDFS student Chris Woywode with Central School Elementary Students, May 1980; 722; 15 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #17 & 18: John Ford in class and John Ford in Syracuse, New York, Feb. 1980; 722; 72 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #19: Micro teaching in Groton High School, Apr. 24, 1980; 722; 11 (Box 18)
  - Sheets 20-23: Campus scenes HE and Ag. Pac on last day of classes, Spring 1980, May 1980; 722; 90 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #24: Cornell Advisory Council Meeting in MVR Faculty Commons, Apr. 1980; 722; 29 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #25: Minority students Admissions Dinner meeting in MVR Faculty Commons, Apr. 1980; 722; 36 (Box 18)
  - Sheet #26: HE Admissions Advisory Training, Apr. 1980; 722; 12 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #27-28: Wendy Wallet--HDFS Professor at Schulyer County Family Resource Center, May 1980; 722; 40 (Box 18)
  - Sheets #29 & 30: Laura Gardner, DNS student--Field Placement at Mt. Sinai/NYC, nd; 722; 51 (Box 18)
  - Sheet # 31: Frances Wong--Field Study/NYC Chinatown, nd; 722; 36 (Box 18)